listeffects.com 2015-12-27

# Free Email List Builder & Year Long Giveaway Event | Opt In Marketing

List Effects Privacy Policy

##### Welcome to List Effects (the "Site")

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business.   
This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site ("Visitors") who visit without transacting business and Visitors who make use of the advertising services offered by List Effects (collectively, "Advertisers") and Visitors who register in the Program ("Authorized Subscribers").

##### "Personally Identifiable Information"

Refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, email address,. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

##### What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?

We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Subscribers: the names, addresses, and email addresses of Authorized Subscribers. If the Visitor came through a referral link, we will attempt to store a cookie on their browser that indicates who referred them. This is to provide credit to the Authorized Member if the Visitor joins.

##### What organizations are collecting the information? 

In addition to our direct collection of information, our third party service vendors (such as credit card companies, clearinghouses and banks) who may provide such services as payment processing of purchased advertising may collect this information from our Advertisers. We do not control how these third parties use such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Advertisers. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them.

##### How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?

We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill advertising requests on the Site. We may email Authorized Subscribers about research or advertising opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Authorized Subscribers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information.

##### With whom may the information may be shared?

Personally Identifiable Information about Authorized Subscribers may be shared with other Authorized Subscribers who wish to evaluate potential transactions with other Authorized Subscribers; Specifically downlines. We may share aggregated information about our Visitors, including the demographics of our Visitors and Authorized Subscribers, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf.

** We will not sell, rent, or otherwise distribute any email addresses from our databases!

##### How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?

Personally Identifiable Information collected by List Effects is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of List Effects , except for use as indicated above.

##### What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?

Visitors, Advertisers, and Authorized Subscribers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, by deleting Authorized Member's account, or by contacting us at admin at listeffects dot com.

##### Are Cookies Used on the Site?

Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Subscribers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is logged on, cookies are used for session authentication.

##### How does List Effects use login information? 

List Effects uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.

##### What partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors, Advertisers, and/or Authorized Subscribers on the Site?

List Effects discloses Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors, Advertisers, and Authorized Subscribers.

##### How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?

All of our employees are familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors, Advertisers, and Authorized Subscribers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors, Advertisers, or Authorized Subscribers for any such occurrences.

##### How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?

Visitors, Advertisers, and Authorized Subscribers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at admin at listeffects dot com. Authorized Subscribers can update Personally Identifiable Information in the Profile section of their member's area.

##### Can a Visitor delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable Information collected by the Site?

We provide Visitors, Advertisers, and Authorized Subscribers with a mechanism to delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site's database by contacting admin at listeffects dot com. However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Visitor's entry without retaining some residual information. An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will have this information functionally deleted.

##### What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?

We will let our Visitors, Advertisers, and Authorized Subscribers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor, Advertiser, or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor, Advertiser, or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor, Advertiser or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure.

##### PLEASE NOTE:

This Site is not directed at children. Visitors, Advertisers, and Authorized Subscribers must be eighteen years or older.

##### Links:

This web site contains links to other web sites, either from our Advertisers, or to Programs listed in the Site. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

Unauthorized duplication or publication of any materials from this Site is expressly prohibited.
